foreign
I got a stain on my button down I have
an interview today I need to get out
that that thing shows like no titty do
you want the job or do you want to waste
your time I need to get the
stain out wow not gonna get it out like
that dude I'm sorry it just cost me 58
bucks what was the thing that your
grandmother used to do the secret trip
tomato juice juice of tomato tomato
juice you sure
yep all right let me see hold on
God I love weed okay all right I don't
have tomato juice but I have Bloody Mary
Max oh that's even better the
horseradish will exfoliate the stain
awesome
okay here we go
okay so do I do I rub it in yes rub it
in smart good it's like is it working I
don't know if it's making it look better
wait you did you applied
did I put the yeah you just watched me
do the whole thing I just remembered
that that was the wrong trick tomato
juice is for skunk sprays are you you
know what I realized her trick was a
couple drops of detergent on the stain
and then you let it sit and then you
wash it normally do you have time for
that her trick was pre-treating a stain
we all know
had a pre-treat a stained Grandma hey
turn that pout Inside Out Sister because
you know what now you have no choice but
to show your freaking titties and that's
how you're gonna get a damn job in this
city town
you think I could go like this go like
this take the pants off I'm going to
interview to be a docent at the frick
yeah well your ass is more powerful than
your tits sorry let me just get my bag
and then I have to go
oh yeah there it is
get that job you know what I am
gonna get that job you know why because
I love the frick
bend over a bunch
foreign